[
  {
    "question": "What command is used to count the total number of lines, words, and characters contained in a file?",
    "options": {
      "A": "countw",
      "B": "wcount",
      "C": "wc",
      "D": "count p"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What command is used to remove files?",
    "options": {
      "A": "dm",
      "B": "rm",
      "C": "delete",
      "D": "erase"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "What command is used to remove the directory?",
    "options": {
      "A": "rdir",
      "B": "remove",
      "C": "rd",
      "D": "rmdir"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What command is used with vi editor to delete a single character?",
    "options": {
      "A": "x",
      "B": "y",
      "C": "a",
      "D": "z"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "What hardware architectures are not supported by Red Hat?",
    "options": {
      "A": "SPARC",
      "B": "IBM-compatible",
      "C": "Alpha",
      "D": "Macintosh"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "The physical layer of a network",
    "options": {
      "A": "constructs packets of data and sends them across the network",
      "B": "controls error detection and correction",
      "C": "defines the electrical characteristics of signals passed between the computer and communication devices",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What TCP/IP protocol is used for remote terminal connection service?",
    "options": {
      "A": "UDP",
      "B": "RARP",
      "C": "FTP",
      "D": "TELNET"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many networks and nodes per network, are allowed by the Class B network?",
    "options": {
      "A": "127 networks and 16,777,216 nodes per network",
      "B": "16,384 networks and 65,534 nodes per network",
      "C": "2,097,152 networks and 254 nodes per network",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "What service is used to translate domain names to IP addresses?",
    "options": {
      "A": "NFS",
      "B": "SMB",
      "C": "NIS",
      "D": "DNS"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following command is used to create a Linux installation boot floppy?",
    "options": {
      "A": "mkboot disk",
      "B": "bootfp disk",
      "C": "ww and rawwrite",
      "D": "dd and rawrite"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you add Amit, a new user, to your system?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Using useradd",
      "B": "Using adduser",
      "C": "Using linuxconf",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does FSF stand for?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Free Software File",
      "B": "File Server First",
      "C": "First Serve First",
      "D": "Free Software Foundation"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  }
]